course, includes the
course, includes
failures along the
way. And then
most provocatively, and
most provocatively,
Shay has done
an amazing job
amazing job
of documenting
what a cure
is going to
is going
be worth.
And I have
to give Brett
give Brett
Winton incredible
credit as he
partnered with
Shay on this
project to try
and figure out
figure out
how much is
how much
a cure worth.
And we think
while the cure
we think
for HAE, which
is a very
HAE, which
rare disease,
would be worth
$11 million.
One and done.
One and
You get this
treatment and
you're done.
That's Intellia's
trial right now,
and it's
in vivo.
You don't have
to go through
go through
any excruciating
preconditioning. It
could be worth
11 million.
That's how much
That's how
it would save
the system.